novaexchange.com 2018-06-24

# Novaexchange - Your Crypto Currency Exchange Engine

## 1\. PRIVACY POLICY

1.1. Goobit Exchange AB ("Goobit") is the entity legally responsible and administering the information submitted via NOVA. Personal data hereinafter applies to all kinds of information which, directly or indirectly, can be attributed to a living natural person.

1.2. Goobit applies the following guidelines for its processing of personal data. Goobit protects the privacy of its customers and process all personal data in accordance with the Swedish law.

1.3. Goobit collects and uses the following personal data: name, email address, telephone number, personal-/social security number, IP-address, order and customer data. Goobit collects the data upon customer's registration with Goobit, if the Customer voluntarily provides information to Goobit via the NOVA, for example, for surveys or in communication with Goobit. Goobit can also, in some cases, collect information from public records. 

1.4. Goobits collection and process of personal data is for the following purposes; 

a) to carry out the Services to the Customer,

b) to ensure the technical functioning of the Services and to prevent use of the Services in breach of the terms of use,

c) to send alerts or messages by email or text messages to the Customer, including to provide the Customer with marketing of Goobit and its related parties' products and services,

d) to send surveys to the Customer regarding the Services,

and is based on the following legal merits;

a) to fulfil requirements by law.

b) to comply with the agreement with the Customer,

1.5. Personal data may be transferred to other companies within the Goobit group, or to business partners of Goobit to perform certain tasks that a customer has requested (for example upon payment), or to comply with these Terms. Goobit may transfer personal information outside of the EU/EEA where you may have less legal rights in relation to your personal data, for the purposes set out in the clause above.

1.6. Disclosure of personal data if strictly needed - Personal Data may be disclosed, if it is necessary, in order to comply with applicable law or request from authorities, to preserve our legal interests or to detect, prevent, or pay attention to fraud and other security or technical matters.

1.7. By clicking the "I accept" button in the user account set up flow at NOVA you agree to the processing of personal data as set out in this Privacy Policy and to receive direct marketing from us or related third parties, e.g. by email or otherwise. 

1.8. Time period - We will process Your Personal Data for the effective time period of the agreement, and we shall delete or anonymise any Personal Data as soon as permitted under Swedish law when the agreement has expired or has been terminated.

1.5. Goobit makes every effort to take all the necessary technical and organizational measures to protect the personal data it processes, so that the data is not lost, destroyed, manipulated, or becomes available to unauthorized persons. We strive to, at our best efforts, achieve and uphold an adequate level of integrity for Your Personal Data as required by law.

1.6. Access requests - Goobit will provide You with the ability to request a record of any Personal Data processed by us and to obtain a transcript of the Personal Data that we as the data controller hold about You, free of charge. We will at Your request or by own initiative correct information found to be incorrect or misleading. We will provide You with the ability to object to the processing of Your Personal Data if such processing is not reasonably required for a legitimate business purpose as described in this Privacy Policy or for our compliance with relevant law. Any request to rectify, anonymize or delete Personal Data will be subject to applicable legal reporting and retention obligations.

1.7. Subcontractor – Goobit may from time to time choose to subcontract the parts of our services and storage, including Your Personal Data, to a third-party Service Provider. This sub data processor will be obliged to follow the same obligations as Goobit when processing Your Personal Data.

1.9. You can object to the use of your personal data at any time and revoke the consent to use your data that you provided upon your registration. You have the right to refuse your personal data being used for direct marketing. In addition, you can request rectification, erasure or blocking at any time of any personal data that is inaccurate. We make explicit reference to the fact that we are obligated by law to continue to save the data; in this case, the data can only be blocked.

1.10. To exercise the aforementioned rights, or if you have any questions about our sharing practices, or wish to have your personal information removed, please contact us at the following address: Goobit Exchange AB, Box 3332, 10367 Stockholm, Sweden. In order to ensure that you receive a swift response, please state in your letter your full name and, if applicable, your address and the email address used for registration. Note that you should sign the request to receive information of the processing of your personal data yourself.

## 2\. COOKIE POLICY

2.1. NOVA website uses so-called "cookies" to enable certain features of bt.cx and novaexchange.com and to create a better user experience when visiting the site. This means that information can be transferred between different web pages, for example, when someone concludes agreement via the website or contacts GOOBIT via the website. Cookies can also be used to track pages impressions in order to improve the design and the usability of the web site. We do not use cookies to record personal data about any of our visitors. Users who do not accept the use of cookies, can change settings in their browser to automatically block them. This can, however, induce that NOVA would no longer work as intended and some functions could not be available.

## 3\. DISPUTE

These terms shall be governed by the substantive laws of Sweden, without reference to the choice of law and conflict of law provisions thereof. Any dispute, claim or controversy arising out of these Terms shall be finally settled by the courts of Sweden

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy as outlined above, please contact Novaexchange at our contact page.
